ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs
1885-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 P N45
8.75 cubic feet
8.8 linear ft.
Photographs.
7461869
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 12, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Scope and Contents
The index for this collection was created by the ILGWU on file cards. The early years (1890 1960) were divided into names followed by subject areas. The second half of the card file (1960-1973) has names and subjects interfiled. P? indicates print with negative though prints and negatives do not always match.
Additional material described by subject headings is available.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780 P: ILGWU Photographs 5780 PNGP: ILGWU Glass Plate Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N35: ILGWU 35mm Negatives of Photographs
Arrangement
Series AF of L
Series Arbitration
Series Agreements
Series Art
Series Big Shot
Series Building- General
Series Brigade
Series Cloak Joint Board
Series Cloak Agreements
Series Cloak out of Town
Series Cloak Welfare Activities
Series Cloak Miscellaneous
Series Dubinsky
Series Eastern out of town
Series Education
Series Educational Meetings
Series Elections
Series Engineering
Series Floats
Series General Ex. Board
Series I.C.F.T.U
Series Housing
Series Staff ILG
Series Impartial Chairman Board and Cloak
Series International Visitors
Series Israel
Series Justice
Series American Labor Party
Series Masquerade, 1936, 1936
Series Masquerade, 1937, 1937
Series May Day, 1937, 1937
Series Meetings ILGWU
Series Meetings Outdoor
Series Miscellaneous
Series African American Activities
Series Northeast Department
Series Organization Department
Series O.R.T
Series Parades
Series Parties
Series Pins and Needles
Series Political
Series Price Settlement
Series Puerto Rico
Series Exhibits: Arts and Crafts
Series Chess
Series Ceramics
Series Chorus
Series Dancing
Series Drawing Painting
Series Sculpture
Series Theater and Stage
Series Gymnastic
Series Hand loom weaving class
Series Leather Craft
Series Players Musicians
Series Miscellaneous
Series Sports General
Series Sports
Series Baseball
Series Basketball
Series Bowling
Series Gymnastics
Series Swimming
Series Tennis
Series Research Department
Series Retirees General
Series Local 9
Series Local 10
Series Local 22, 1922
Series Local 25
Series Local 32
Series Local 35
Series Local 38
Series Local 48
Series Local 60
Series Local 62
Series Local 89
Series Local 105
Series Local 117
Series Local 142
Series Local 155
Series Shop Party
Series Taft Hartley
Series Training Institute
Series Union Health Center
Series Union Label
Series Unity House
Series War Effort
Series Ship launching
Series Welfare
Series West Virginia
Series WFDR
Series Amun Isreali
Series Amperex
Series Beer
Series Berman, Jack
Series Chan
Series Deborah San
Series Foreign Policy Assoc. World Affairs Center for the U.S.
Series I.B.E.W. Local 3, 19 3
Series ICFTU
Series International Hand Bag Luggage W.V.
Series IVE CIO
Series Kaufman
Series 32 B Local
Series Painters Local 186, 137 Gaffe Street New Haven Connecticut
Series Plumbers Local 2, 132- 4th Avenue
Series Miscellaneous
Series Shoe workers
Series Newspaper Guild
Series Textile Workers Union
Series T.W.U.
Series WLIB
Series Local 9
Series Local 10
Series Local 22, 1922
Series Children of Local 22
Series Local 23
Series Local 25, 1925
Series Local 30, 1930
Series Local 32
Series Local 35, 1935
Series Local 38
Series Local 40
Series Local 48
Series Local 60
Series Local 62
Series Local 64
Series Local 66, 1966
Series Local 82, 1982
Series Local 89
Series Local 91, 1991
Series Local 93, 1993
Series Local 98, 1998
Series Local 99
Series Local 102
Series Local 105
Series Local 117
Series Local 121
Series Local 124
Series Local 132
Series Local 135
Series Local 138
Series Local 142
Series Local 155
Series Local 177
Series Local 481
Series Miscellaneous
Series AL
Series Labor Stage
Series Labor Stage Portraits
Series Miscellaneous
Clothing workers -- Labor unions; Textile workers -- Labor unions
7461869
- Abromowitz; Louis Nelson, Local 155; Elias Lieberman at dinner table (item no.1) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Acheson, Dean speaking at a Roosevelt rally (item no.2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Aherne, Tom, portrait (item no.3) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Alfange, D. and Samuel Shore (item no.4) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Alfange, D. and Maida Springer (item no.5) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Alfange, D., and Charles Zimmerman (item no.6) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Altman speaking (item no.7) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Altmeyer, Harry, speaking (item no.8) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Altmeyer, Harry; Nagler and Antonini (item no.9) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Altmeyer, Harry; Nagler and Antonini (item no.10) (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Amter speaking (item no.11) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Anderson, Mary, shapshot (item no.12) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Antonini Portrait, 1936 (item no.13) (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Antonini Mr. & Mrs. Antonini (item no.14) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Antonini Mr. & Mrs. Antonini (item no.15) (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Antonini with Wendell Wilkie (item no.16) (Box 3, Folder 16)
- David Dubinsky, Jean and Mrs Dubinsky at White House (item no.16A) (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Antonini showing Democratic book (item no.17) (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Antonini Painting of Antonini (item no.18) (Box 3, Folder 19)
- David Dubinsky, Father Bezalel, and sister in Lady Poland in 1931 (item no.18A) (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Antonini Artist with painting (item no.19) (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Split with CIO M.D. Danish and David Dubinsky 11/11/1938 (item no.19A) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Scope and Contents
  November 11th
- Antonini Close up of painting (item no.20) (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Antonini Mr. & Mrs. Antonini disembarking from boat (item no.21) (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Antonini Mr. & Mrs. Antonini (with bouquet) on return from tour of Italy (item no.22) (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Antonini Greeting friends at dock on return from Italy (item no.23) (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Antonini making broadcast (Mutual) (item no.24) (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Antonini with globe of the world (item no.25) (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Antonini portrait (signing paper) (item no.26) (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Antonini shaking hands with Grover Walen (Dubinsky looks on) (item no.27) (Box 3, Folder 30)
- David Dubinsky picket by employees at Unity Party 1948 (item no.28) (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Antonini with John Gelo, Charles Zimmerman, and J. Hochman (item no.28A) (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Antonini speaking at Worlds Fair, 1940 (item no.29) (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Antonini portrait at desk (item no.30) (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Antonini, Mr. & Mrs. Antonini; Mr. & Mrs. J.Gelo at dinner (item no.31) (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Antonini speaking (Local 89 broadcast) (item no.32) (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Antonini speaking at dinner with Count Sforza (OWI) (item no.33) (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Antonini speaking at dinner (Count Sforza, Dubinsky) (item no.34) (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Antonini reclining behind desk (candid) (item no.35) (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Antonini speaking at dinner (John Gelo, C. Zimmerman, Alex Rose) (item no.36) (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Antonini at broadcast (Local 25, WEVD) (item no.37) (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Antonini at broadcast (Local 25, WEVD) (item no.38) (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Antonini portrait (item no.39) (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Antonini speaking (item no.40) (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Antonini speaking (item no.41) (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Antonini speaking (item no.42) (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Antonini speaking (item no.43) (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Antonini speaking (item no.44) (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Aronsky, Charles, portrait at desk (item no.45) (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Backer, George portrait (item no.46) (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Ashbes portrait (item no.47) (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Bagno, Morris portraits, several poses (item no.48) (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Balabanof, Angelica speaking (item no.49) (Box 3, Folder 53)
- International Ladies Garment Workers UnionTraining Institute (item no.50), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  Opening May 1, 1950, photos of students, teachers, speakers; including Hochman, DUBINSKY, Elder, Umhey, Irwin L H Kerrison, Dean Martoin P. Catherwood of Cornell
- Baron, Murray portraits, 7/3/52, 11 W 42nd St (item no.51), 1952 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  July 3rd
- Baskin speaking (item no.52) (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Berger, Sam (Local 102) portrait at desk (item no.53) (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Berger, Sam (Local 102) portrait (item no.54) (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Berle, Adolph speaking at dinner (item no.55) (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Berle, Adolph speaking (item no.55A) (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Berle, Adolph speaking (CBS) (item no.56) (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Berle, Adolph and Antonini at dinner (item no.57) (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Berle, Adolph speaking (item no.58) (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Berle, Adolph speaking at dinner (OWI), Antonini and Count Sforza (item no.59) (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Bernstein, Charles portrait (item no.60) (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Bernstein, Charles with notebook at table (item no.61) (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Bevin, Ernest with Dubinsky and George Meany (item no.62) (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Bevin, Ernest with Dubinsky, George Meany, and Matthew Wohl (item no.63) (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Bevin, Ernest with Dubinsky, George Meany, and Matthew Wohl (Al and Dick in back) (item no.64) (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Bevin, Ernest speaking (item no.65) (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Bregman, Bob portrait in uniform (item no.66) (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Victor Alter portrait (item no.66A) (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Victor Alter portrait (item no.66B) (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Henry R. Erlich portrait (item no.67) (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Henry R. Erlich portrait (original) (item no.67A) (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Bialis, Morris at desk with secretary (item no.67B) (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Bialis, Morris portrait (2 negatives; 1 with mustache, 1 without), 4/9/53 (item no.68), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  April 9th (2 negatives; 1 with mustache, 1 without)
- Billings speaking, Dubinsky applauding in back (item no.69) (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Bluestein, Max portrait, 3/57 (item no.70), 1957 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  March
- Blum, Leon speaking (item no.71) (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Boland, Father speaking (item no.72) (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Boyer, Arthur portrait (item no.73) (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Brandt portrait (item no.74) (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Breslaw, Isidore speaking (item no.75) (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Breslau, Joseph portrait (item no.76) (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Bridges, Harry speaking (item no.77) (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Bridges, Harry, Joe Curran, Charles Zimmerman (item no.78) (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Bronstein, Harry portrait at desk (item no.79) (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Broune, Hayward speaking (2 negatives) (item no.80) (Box 3, Folder 89)
  (2 negatives)
- Chan, Sou portrait (item no.81) (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Brown, Irving seated speaking in Paris, 1952 (item no.82) (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Brown, Irving portrait (item no.83) (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Chan, Sou picture of House of Chan Restaurant (item no.84) (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Chan, Sou eating with chopsticks (item no.85) (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Browder, Earl portrait (item no.86) (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Browder, Earl candid shot with hand raised (item no.87) (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Chan, Sou with Uncle Chan, David Dubinsky, Woltman, Mileton, and Josh Logan (item no.88) (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Clapper, Mrs. Raymond portrait (item no.89) (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Clark, General and Julius Hochman (item no.90) (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Starr, Mark in group (item no.91) (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Clothy, Bill (Rainwear) portrait (item no.92) (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Cohn, Fannia portraits at desk (3 negatives) (item no.93) (Box 3, Folder 102)
  (3 negatives)
- Cohn, Fannia portrait and speaking, 4/18/53 (item no.94), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  April 18th
- Cohen, Martin L. portrait and at desk, 7/55 (item no.95), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  July
- Connelly, Eugene portrait at desk (2 negatives) (item no.96) (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Corey, Louis speaking (item no.97) (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Corey, Louis portrait at desk (item no.98) (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Cottone, Anthony portrait (item no.99) (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Crone, Harry portraits (item no.100) (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Curran, Joe speaking (item no.101) (Box 3, Folder 110)
- Brent, Alice portrait at desk (item no.102) (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Brick, Alexander portrait (item no.103) (Box 3, Folder 112)
- Chevenalls (Belgian Labor Leader) speaking (2 negatives) (item no.104) (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Counts, George S. with Dubinsky & Mrs. Roosevelt & portrait (item no.105) (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Chiang Ki Chek, Madame with Thomas Dewey (item no.106) (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Childs, Marquis speaking over WFranklin D. Roosevelt (item no.107) (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Chiang Ki Chek, Madame speaking (item no.108) (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Chiang Ki Chek, Madame seated on platform (item no.109) (Box 3, Folder 118)
- Broune, Hayward candid at typewriter (8x10 negatives) (item no.110) (Box 3, Folder 119)
  (8x10 negatives)
- Brown, Irving and Mrs. Brown at IRRC Luncheon (item no.111) (Box 3, Folder 120)
- Cohen, Martin L. and Edward Molisani (item no.112) (Box 3, Folder 121)
- Molisani, Edward and Marty Cohen (item no.112) (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Cooper baby (item no.113) (Box 3, Folder 123)
- Cohen, Max with Mrs. Cohen and daughter at a dinner (item no.114) (Box 3, Folder 124)
- Crosswaith, Frank and LaGuardia (item no.115) (Box 3, Folder 125)
- Crosswaith, Frank speaking (item no.116) (Box 3, Folder 126)
- Crosswaith, Frank with Dubinsky & William Green (item no.117), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  Harlem Labor Committee, 1940, New York Convention
- Citrine, Sir Walter speaking (item no.118) (Box 3, Folder 128)
- Citrine, Sir Walter portrait (item no.119) (Box 3, Folder 129)
- Citrine, Sir Walter and Matthew Woll (item no.120) (Box 3, Folder 130)
- Danish, Max portrait, 5/51 (item no.121), 1951 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  May
- Danish, Max portrait (item no.122) (Box 3, Folder 132)
- Danish, Max speaking (item no.123) (Box 3, Folder 133)
- Danish, Max Danishs baby (item no.124) (Box 3, Folder 134)
- Danish, Max with Helen Rooney (item no.125) (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Danish, Max with Harry Crone (item no.126) (Box 3, Folder 136)
- Danish, Max portrait standing behind chair (item no.127) (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Danish, Max portrait seated (item no.128) (Box 3, Folder 138)
- Danish, Max portrait (item no.129) (Box 3, Folder 139)
- Davis, William H. portrait (item no.130) (Box 3, Folder 140)
- Rios, Delos speaking at Spanish rally; Madison Square Garden (item no.131) (Box 3, Folder 141)
- DeMargio, Margaret portrait (item no.132) (Box 3, Folder 142)
- Dewey, Thomas E. speaking over station WEVD (item no.133) (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Dewey, Thomas E. shaking hands with DUBINSKY (item no.134) (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Dewey, Thomas E. speaking (Alex Rose applauding) (item no.135) (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Dewey, Thomas E. in tuxedo (item no.136) (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Dewey, Thomas E. speaking (Local 22) (item no.137) (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Durham, Mabel portrait (item no.138) (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Extract, Morris portrait (item no.139) (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Falikman, Moe portraits; 9/10/52, 1959 official (item no.140), 1952 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  September 10th
- Donovan, General and Frankenthaler (item no.141) (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Frankenthaler, Judge speaking (item no.142) (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Donovan, General speaking (item no.143) (Box 3, Folder 153)
- DeBrouckere, Louis (Senator) speaking (item no.144) (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Danish, Max with European delegation (item no.145) (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Danish, Max throwing ball (item no.146) (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Danish, Max speaking on radio (item no.147) (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Danish, Max Danishs son Roy (item no.148) (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Danish, Max Danishs weDavid Dubinskying (item no.149) (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Danish, Max laughing with friend (item no.150) (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Shaplen, Joe (deceased) NY Times labor reporter, at dinner, DUBINSKY speaking, Danish and Hardman (item no.151) (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Danish, Max with Dubinsky and Hardman (item no.152) (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Danish, Max being kissed, Dubinsky signing paper (item no.153) (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Danish, Max speaking at dinner, Dubinsky, Hardman (item no.154) (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Danish, Max at dinner, Hardman speaking, Dubinsky (item no.155) (Box 3, Folder 165)
- Einstein, Albert and Julius Hochman with Pins and Needles cast (item no.156) (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Danish, Max candid at typewriter with no shirt (item no.157) (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Danish, Max carrying picket sign at 1940 Convention with Mary Jane Miller (item no.158) (Box 3, Folder 168)
- Danish, Max with soldier (item no.159) (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Dewey, Thomas E. with Mrs. Dewey and Luigi Antonini (item no.160) (Box 3, Folder 170)
- Dewey, Thomas E. speaking while photographer snaps picture (item no.161) (Box 3, Folder 171)
- Dubinsky, Emma and Samuel Shore (item no.162) (Box 3, Folder 172)
- Erlich, Eve with two youngsters (item no.163) (Box 3, Folder 173)
- Erlich, Eve portrait (item no.164) (Box 3, Folder 174)
- Dubow, Lou candid (item no.165) (Box 3, Folder 175)
- Erlich, Eve portrait (item no.166) (Box 3, Folder 176)
- Erlich, Eve and Sy Hamburger (item no.167) (Box 3, Folder 177)
- Douglas, Melvin (actor) at Local 22 Educational meeting (item no.168) (Box 3, Folder 178)
- Faulkner, Harold U., Mark Starr and Joseph Tuvim radio program (item no.169) (Box 3, Folder 179)
- Farber, Simon portrait at desk (item no.170) (Box 3, Folder 180)
- Farber, Simon and family (item no.171) (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Feinberg, Israel talking on phone (item no.172) (Box 3, Folder 182)
- Feinberg, Israel and Pearl L. Willen (item no.173) (Box 3, Folder 183)
- Feinberg, Israel, Mr. and Mrs. George Rubin (50th Anniversary Dinner) (item no.174) (Box 3, Folder 184)
- Feinberg, Israel speaking (item no.175) (Box 3, Folder 185)
- Feinberg, Israel portrait (item no.176) (Box 3, Folder 186)
- Feinberg, Israel and Jimmy Walker (item no.177) (Box 3, Folder 187)
- Feldman, Martin speaking (item no.178) (Box 3, Folder 188)
- Fleming, Colonel speaking (item no.179) (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Fish, Hy portrait (item no.180) (Box 3, Folder 190)
- Farrell, James T. with union educators (item no.181) (Box 3, Folder 191)
- Fox, Phil portrait with whistle (item no.182) (Box 3, Folder 192)
- Fox, Phil portrait (item no.183) (Box 3, Folder 193)
- France, Shirley May and her mother, 9/14/49 (item no.184), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  September
- Freedman, Zachary L. speaking at dinner; Umhey seated (item no.185) (Box 3, Folder 195)
- Freedman, Zachary L. speaking (item no.186) (Box 3, Folder 196)
- Freedman, Zachary L. and bowling champs (item no.187) (Box 3, Folder 197)
- Geller, Edward portrait (item no.188) (Box 3, Folder 198)
- Gelo, John portrait (item no.189) (Box 3, Folder 199)
- Gelo, John speaking (item no.190) (Box 3, Folder 200)
- Granger, Lester and Charles Zimmerman (item no.191) (Box 3, Folder 201)
- Frankenthaler, Judge portrait (item no.192) (Box 3, Folder 202)
- Frankenthaler, Judge and conciliatory board (item no.193) (Box 3, Folder 203)
- Gingold, David speaking, speaking at mike at dress strike, 3/58 (item no.194), 1958 (Box 3, Folder 204)
- Gingold, David portrait (3 negatives) plus 8x10 negative (item no.195) (Box 3, Folder 205)
  (3 negatives) plus 8x10 negative
- Gingold, David painting (item no.196) (Box 3, Folder 206)
- Gingold, David and Mike Johnson (item no.197) (Box 3, Folder 207)
- Gladstone, Joseph portrait (item no.198) (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Glushein, Morris (Attorney) portrait (item no.199) (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Lewis, Willard portrait (item no.200) (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Gladstone, Joseph and wife (item no.201) (Box 3, Folder 211)
- Goff, Mary portrait (item no.202) (Box 3, Folder 212)
- Goldman, Emma portrait (item no.203) (Box 3, Folder 213)
- Goldman, Emma in Spain (item no.204) (Box 3, Folder 214)
- Goldman, Emma at street corner meeting (item no.205) (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Gomberg, William candid (item no.206) (Box 3, Folder 216)
- Gomberg, William portrait (item no.207) (Box 3, Folder 217)
- Gomberg, William portrait at desk (item no.208) (Box 3, Folder 218)
- Gomberg, William portrait, 4 negatives (item no.209) (Box 3, Folder 219)
- Gomberg, William with desk full of cameras (item no.210) (Box 3, Folder 220)
- Goodman, Benny and band broadcasting over WNYC (item no.211) (Box 3, Folder 221)
- Green, William speaking (item no.212) (Box 3, Folder 222)
- Green, William portrait (item no.213) (Box 3, Folder 223)
- Dubinsky and Greene on platform, James Corey 4/11/1943 (item no.214) (Box 3, Folder 224)
  April 11th
- Green, William speaking, hands upraised (item no.215) (Box 3, Folder 225)
- Dubinsky with Judge Goldstein and Stulberg (item no.216) (Box 3, Folder 226)
- Goldstein, Judge aDavid Dubinskyresses Local 66 (item no.217) (Box 3, Folder 227)
- MacLauren, Ben and Judge Goldstein (item no.218) (Box 3, Folder 228)
- Green, William and Louis Schaefer (item no.219) (Box 3, Folder 229)
- Gladstone, Joseph and son (item no.220) (Box 3, Folder 230)
- Guzman portrait at desk (item no.221) (Box 3, Folder 231)
- Dubinsky, Harry Greenberg speaking (item no.222) (Box 3, Folder 232)
- Greenberg, Harry speaking Local 91 (item no.223) (Box 3, Folder 233)
- Greenberg, Harry in office (item no.224) (Box 3, Folder 234)
- Greenberg, Harry portrait (2 negatives) (item no.225) (Box 3, Folder 235)
- Greenberg, Harry portrait in bow tie, 1959 New York Times Supplement (item no.226) (Box 3, Folder 236)
- Greene, Sol and Harry Greenberg (item no.227) (Box 3, Folder 237)
- Greenberg, Harry speaking at dinner (item no.228) (Box 3, Folder 238)
- Pankin, Judge with LaGuardia Judge H. Greenberg speaking (item no.229) (Box 3, Folder 239)
- LaGuardia, Judge Pankin on platform; J. Walker speaking (item no.230) (Box 3, Folder 240)
- LaGuardia speaking (item no.231) (Box 3, Folder 241)
- Gross, Murray portrait (item no.232) (Box 3, Folder 242)
- Gross, Murray and daughter (item no.233) (Box 3, Folder 243)
- Grossman, Herman portraits (item no.234) (Box 3, Folder 244)
- Schlesinger, Jack portrait, 1950 (item no.1) (Box 4, Folder 1)